

MAFALDA NICOLAU

Aspiring UX & UI Designer

OBJECTIVE

I am a fast-learning woman who likes to work meticulous at a high pace, both individually and in a team, and is also a quick-witted problem solver when needed.

I graduated three years ago from a Technology program specializing in information and media technology in Järfälla Gymnasium and now studying further at Chas Academy to become a UX/UI Designer, where I will graduate in the spring of 2024.

With my knowledge in both design and frontend development, I am ready to contribute to exciting projects and learn even more in the industry on an internship position during week 46-2023 until week 17-2024. Are you my new employer?

EXPERIENCE

TEAM LEADER/KEY USER • ICA GRUPPEN AB • 08/2021-ONGOING

Group manager's right hand and possess the skill to replace staff in any of the different task assignments in the warehouse. Responsible for the introduction to the workplace and teach new employees. Keep track of all departments in the warehouse, goods receipt, pick stations and the unloading process. Solve different problems that occur during the day. Operating counterbalanced forklift.

TECHNICAL INTERN • ERICSSON RADIO SYSTEMS AB• 01/2021-05/2021

Internship arranged by *Tekniksprånget* at Ericsson Radio Systems AB (*Tekniksprånget* is an internship program run by the Royal Academy of Engineering Sciences (IVA), where Sweden's employers, together with the government, are investing in securing the supply of skills for the future.)

By shadowing civil engineers, I got the chance to get close to their tasks and responsibilities. During this time, I was responsible for certain presentations and mailings of the department's monthly letters with summaries of various project in the radio development area.

WAREHOUSE ASSOCIATE • ARLA FOODS • 04/2020-08/2021

Operated low lift truck to prepare orders of milk products from stores in Stockholm. Worked with rotating shift 24/7 and often under high tempo. Excelled when put in stressful situations.

SALES ASSOCIATE • THE FOOD WORLD • 06/2017-04/2018

Enhanced customer satisfaction ratings by resolving issues efficiently. Replenished floor stock and processed shipments to provide product availability for customers.

Addressed customer inquiries and concerns to facilitate decision-making and minimize anxiety or hesitation.

Assisted customers with product selection and sales.







SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Javascript

React

Wordpress

Git

Figma

Microsoft Office

Adobe illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Advanced: English + Spanish

Native: Swedish + Portuguese

Automatic driver's license Truck driver's license (type A1-4 & B1)

EDUCATION

UX/UI - DESIGNER WITH FRONTEND COMPETENS • 2022-2024 • CHAS ACADEMY

TECHNOLOGY PROGRAMME WITH SPECIALIZATION INFORMATION AND MEDIA TECNOLOGY • 2017-2020 • JÄRFÄLLA GYMNASIUM SWEDEN

PERSONAL CHARACTERISTICS

- AMBITIOUS
- RESPONSIBLE
- ORDERLY
- METICULOUS
- EFFECTIVE
- QUICK LEARNING
- CARING
- POSITIVE
- •SOCIAL
- UNIQUE





